{
    "id": "999d7f4b66d246438ecabb377266be7a",
    "title": "Combine using a conjunction or a relative pronoun",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "575a443b5c924a479b86a02c6f557dcc",
            "title": "Conjunctions And Relative Pronouns Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Her clothes caught fire ................................................. she was cooking in the kitchen.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "while",
                        "since",
                        "whereas"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................... his sons are employed, he has no financial worries.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "That",
                        "Now that",
                        "So that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He does not know any language ........................................... Hindi.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "apart",
                        "except",
                        "expect"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................... I invited them, they did not come.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Even if",
                        "Even though",
                        "If"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................................... the weather was bad, he went out.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "As",
                        "As though",
                        "Though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Julius Caesar, .................................................. came to Britain in 55 BC, was a powerful Roman General.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "that",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................... the clock struck twelve, I went to bed.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "When",
                        "Since",
                        "Until"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Napoleon, ............................................. the French honor very much, died at St. Helena.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "whom",
                        "which",
                        "that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is the new computer ............................................... my father bought yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "what",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The village ......................................... we live is infested with rats.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "where",
                        "that",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}